

REACT JS / BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

#### **Details**

9558580469

mohammedlokhand4429@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Indian

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

16/11/2000

Ahmedabad

## Links

Portfolio

<u>Twitter</u>

<u>LinkedIn</u>

# **Skills**React js

JavaScript

Blockchain

Solidity

Web3.js

NodeJS

HTML5

Truffle

Bootstrap

GitHub

Git

### **Profile**

Hi, I'm Mohammed, a skilled **Front-end and Blockchain developer** with 1.5 years of experience in **React Js**, **Angular**, **and Smart Contract** development. I've contributed to web3 open source projects and am open to all project types. I value clear communication and strive for success through collaboration. Let's create something great together!

## **Employment History**

Blockchain Developer, at Sunflowee Biztech, Ahmedabad

SEPTEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

Frontend Developer, at Arishti Info Labs, Ahmedabad

AUGUST 2021 - AUGUST 2022

## **Education**

B.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering , Indrashil University, Rajpur

## **Project**

#### **UNITE3**, Contribution Power as NFT

- Develop platform using React js for viewing, claiming, and contributing to UNITE3 projects as NFTs.
- Create secure smart contracts in Solidity for NFT transactions and ownership.
- Integrate smart contracts with React js for transparent management of contributions on UNITE3.
- Check out my GitHub Repo: <a href="https://github.com/Mohammed-16/UNITE3">https://github.com/Mohammed-16/UNITE3</a>

## Open Bazzar, NFT marketplace

- Develop NFT marketplace using React js for user-friendly interface.
- Build secure smart contracts in Solidity for NFT transactions.
- Integrate smart contracts with React js for easy NFT trading on Open Bazzar.
- Check out my GitHub Repo: https://github.com/Mohammed-16/OpenBazaar

### Yield Farming, Blockchain

- Developed a DeFi app using Solidity, Web3, Truffle, and React js.
- Optimized usability and implemented Back-end for ERC-20 Token.
- Check out my GitHub Repo: https://github.com/Mohammed-16/Yield-Farming-DeFi-ERC20-Token-

#### **Courses**

Blockchain, Ethereum & Solidity, Udemy

JUNE 2022 - AUGUST 2022

React js, Udemy

JANUARY 2021 - MARCH 2021

## **College Grade**

Sem VIII, 10.00 SGPA

Overall , 8.63 CGPA